This has come up in the meetings. How
much pride do you take in that and how
did you do that? Yeah. Um so I actually
met with the Jets this morning and they
asked me about any times I fumbled in my
Notre Dame career. I said one time it
was against Boise State, the ball came
out. Didn't lose it, but it did come out
and uh
I don't really fumble a lot because I I
like to give the credit to my coach, uh
coach McCullough, Deland McCullough. Uh
he's my running back coach my freshman
sophomore year.
Um I kid you not, the first like the
first warm-up I came into Notre Dame and
like the first warm-up he gave me a ball
like a bigger ball and he like he like
he like create like a a good a good
posture with the ball. Tight tight tight
tight. And I did that for all the
warm-ups and um from then on until all
the games I didn't fumble um because of
what Deland
you know taught me and um
that's pretty much it. That's That's why
I don't fumble. But
he was a good person in high school.
Jack, to your right over there, Jack.
You mentioned in all these meetings
trying to learn as much as you can. What
are some of the biggest things that
you've learned or taken away through
that process?
I would say like I
questions that I go into these meetings
with is how do I fit in this
What can I do to have success you know
on and off the field and what have you
seen players do to
you know
have success in the National Football
League. Those are questions that I ask.
I've learned that consistency,
discipline,
once you get to the league don't change
who you are. Like a lot of times guys
get to the league and they're I made it.
No, you haven't made it. You you ain't
made it past your first contract. You
got to get to that. For me I want to get
to my third contract.
So when I get to my third contract and I
get to that and that's over and I've got
shoot one day I hope I got my gold
jacket. One day I've made shoot Pro Bowl
hopefully five plus years. Um
then I think that you know I've had some
type of success, but those are questions
that I ask when I'm in these meetings
and going to these visits with uh I just
want to know uh how I can get to the
next level. Do you tattoo that like all
these goals are in your mind and how do
you how do you
>> Oh yeah. I tell them that I want to be
one of the best of all time. Want to be
a Pro Bowler and I want to be a Pro
Bowler in my very first year. I want to
make
offensive rookie. I tell them all these
goals uh that I have, but um
I just use them as goals. Those are
goals, um but you got to have a process
for how you going to achieve those
things. So um I'll go
like every season and set out like
little goals like
per week what I can do to achieve make
sure I hit your bigger goal that I have.
And I tell all these teams this and uh
it's a lot of big talk, but I have a
process and I have a plan for how I'm
going
JD, all the way over here to your left,
JD. Um two parts. Uh I saw you had a
warm reception with uh Saints offensive
coordinator Doug Nussmeier today. Um
what has been your contact with that
organization with Mid Atlantic? Second
part is uh obviously you felt pretty
good about what you put on film at the
combine. What did you want to show teams
intellectually and mentally?
So um I had a formal with the Saints.
Um
like you said, I just met coach uh here
at the com- uh pro day at the combine.
Just met over here and talked to him a
little bit before pro day. Um
I mean that's all the interaction we
really had. You know, I've talked to the
running back coach. I've talked to
basically our whole coaching staff and
they're great people over there. You
know, I would love to be a part of that
organization. Uh I feel like I would
bring a lot to the team. Um but I mean
that's pretty much all it is. Like all
the teams I try to present myself the
best way that I can and have great
conversations with all of them and
that's all it was with the Saints.
Hopefully they like me. Hopefully they
pick me if I'm there.
Um that's pretty much it.
JD, right here, the guy in the vest.
Yeah. What's the What's the team getting
in J D McKissic?
Everything you're going to get in me. JD
can do
as much as me or possibly more. He can
do kick return. I can't do kick return.
I can, but I don't do it.
Um but you're going to get everything
you need in a football player, in a
running back, in a receiver, you know,
in a blocker. JD can do it all.
Right here. Go ahead. What does your
preparation look like in your training
for the draft? So um
it's been kind of hard uh to uh make
sure that I'm getting the best of
everything. So training I've been doing
a lot of traveling, so it's hard to
train. Um
I've been doing a lot of talking, uh a
lot of mental stuff goes with you know
going into teams, talking to them about
schemes, talking to them about me as a
person. So uh I've been trying to make
sure I've been very well prepared when
it comes to the mental side, but when it
comes to the physical side, you know,
I've been doing my best to try and work
out here and there. It's pretty It's
really hard. It's a lot going on. A lot
of people coming at me, but I'm doing my
best to try and
get the best of everything.
And what's the biggest thing you valued
in the team at Notre Dame that you want
to see in the NFL?
The brotherhood, you know, the culture.
Um I've met some great people here at
Notre Dame. Um
made some of the best friends that I'll
probably ever have in my life. And um
I'm hoping at the next level I get to do
that same thing. I get to meet great
people, build you know, great
relationships with people and um
you know, just build something that
lasts after football because at the end
of the day the sport is only a short
part of my life and um
I want to
be remembered by the people and I want
to build better relationships with
people. I got four more questions.